foreclosures.com 2018-08-26

# Privacy Policy and Security Statement

### Privacy Policy and Security Statement

**www.foreclosure.com** is dedicated to safeguarding your online privacy. The following explains how your information will be treated as you make use of our products and services. 

#### Your Information

**www.foreclosure.com** draws a distinction between information that is provided when registering online and/or through our mobile application and information that is provided when listing a property on our website. 

#### Personal Information

Personal information is defined as any information entered when registering or using services obtained through our website, information you provide as part of registration for one of applications or any other information collected about you on our platform (such as how long you spend searching, what you are searching, etc.) We at **www.foreclosure.com** constantly strive to provide useful products and tools based on the content of our service and on related subjects of interest. We may sell or distribute certain individual personal information to other companies, including related interests or vendors so as to provide you with important offers. We may also use or provide partners with aggregate information from the information provided by all users. If you linked to this page (or subscription form) from another website, information entered here may be disclosed to the owners of such website and to other third parties. If you are a participant in our educational programs we may provide you special offers on related subjects of interest or an email displaying those subjects. 

#### Cookies

To enhance your visit with personalized services, **www.foreclosure.com** makes use of cookie technology. A cookie is a small file that is assigned to a user when he or she registers online and/or through a mobile device (including tablets, smartphones, iPods, etc.). These cookies do not collect personally identifiable information nor are they shared with our partners and vendors. We use cookie technology to track the way in which customers use the site and/or service so that we can provide them with content that caters to their needs. We also use cookies to make your visit more convenient by saving your sign in information so that you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our site and/or use our service. 

#### IP Address

IP addresses are unique to each computer, and they are used to identify senders and receivers of information over the Internet. **www.foreclosure.com** uses your device's IP address to administer our website and/or mobile application to verify your identity and to report aggregate information to our partners. 

#### Contests and Surveys

**www.foreclosure.com** occasionally asks users to complete surveys that we use for research purposes. This information could be shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis unless you otherwise consent. Individual user information is not released without your consent. 

#### A Word About Security

At **www.foreclosure.com** , we are committed to maintaining a secure environment to store and receive your personal information. 

All of the information transmitted to **www.foreclosure.com** , whether it’s online or through our mobile application, is stored safely and securely behind our firewall. A firewall is a buffer that isolates our network from the Internet. 

At **www.foreclosure.com** , we constantly monitor our web and application security to protect your information. Once your information is received at **www.foreclosure.com** , access to your information is limited. Each employee is provided with a copy of this document so that they are aware of our privacy practices. 

**www.foreclosure.com** works closely with our partners to ensure your privacy, however, we are not responsible for the privacy policy or content of our partners' websites or of third-party vendors. 

Unless otherwise noted herein we will not disclose any of your personal information to third parties, except when we have your permission or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. 

#### Changing and Editing Your Information

You, as a user, can change or edit your personal information at any time. This procedure is accomplished by choosing to edit your profile account information or registration information once logged in on our website or through our mobile application. If you have any difficulties with -- or questions about -- the modification of personal information please contact [support@foreclosure.com](mailto:support@foreclosure.com). 

#### Conclusion

Thank you for taking the time to educate yourself about the ways in which **www.foreclosure.com** collects, uses and stores the information that you provide. We recommend that you also read our Terms and Conditions of Service and Use since it provides more information about **www.foreclosure.com** policies. If you have any questions about our privacy policy and security statement, please contact [support@foreclosure.com](mailto:support@foreclosure.com). Please revisit this site on occasion to make sure that you have viewed the most recent version of the privacy policy and security statement. **www.foreclosure.com** reserves the right to change any of the information listed on this document and will notify users of any changes by posting the new version of this document to the site at the Privacy Policy & Security Statement link. 

top
